Welcome to my channel friends, in today's
video we will talk about how you can get
your bike or car insured sitting at home.
If you have
gone to an agent for a faulty generator,
you might have had to pay extra charges. So
today we will tell you that you
can get your bike insured by clicking on the subscribe button and get your bike insured for
very minimal money.
To get Nexon bike insurance, you will
find videos for many years in which you will have to go to
some site and log in
and give many details,
but the method we will tell you
through the phone is very easy. You
can like and subscribe, so let's go to the
app on the phone, friends, as soon as you
open it, you will have to scroll the full tab
and below it you will see
Bikers step, then you have to
enter the bike number, your bike number, click next
here,
you will have to click on the office hours option. After entering the bike number,
you will remember all the information related to the bike. You will be asked when you
bought the bike and which bike it is.
Okay, this is your previous policy part
that your 24 has expired. If it is done then
you will get this.  If this is going on in your policy, then
you will click on listen.
After clicking, you will have to
click on the person below. After clicking,
you will see some plans from the company. You will
see many plans in it.
Show three alarms in it. You are
getting 1683 rupees for this and 28 rupees for Reliance General
and 1968 rupees for ICICI Lombard.
I will
tell you about all the points, how you
can click on it and how you can
take advantage of its tension condition.
Friends, you have to take this option, click on it
and by clicking on this benefit,
you can see
which benefits you will get under it. Its
point is
for the year and in that, the vehicle which is shown in the valley
at 3691 is accidental death. If
your bike meets with an accident, then
this will be your cover or
damage due to something or if there is a
fire, then there will be a wide impact in it.
Damage due to natural calamity, if
any  Cyclone or earthquake happens, if
a bike gets damaged due to that, then it also gets
cut in some way or if your bike gets stolen, then
you will get theft cover in it
and under third party quality,
you can share this point of view video,
like and subscribe and you can subscribe to this channel,
you can change one option for this and subscribe,
this saver
is 11093 cloth, what will you get under it, in
which only third party like it is there
and many things will not be covered in it,
like if it gets damaged, the
vehicle gets destroyed due to earthquake, natural
disaster, cyclone, it gets stolen,
all these things will be there in it, only
third party insurance will be covered in it, so
we are going to do third party insurance in it,
for this you will have to pay ₹11.70,
you will have to select this plan here and click on this
Chakli, after clicking
all the details you will get, who is the winner of the bike,
which email address has been given, what is the bike
number, what is the recent,
what is the engine number of your bike and chassis number,
all these details will be available to you  There is an option here, if
you have a personal problem then
you will have to pay Rs. 300 separately for that, you
tick here and subscribe, then in this
you do not add anything in it,
then you will have to click on continue,
something like this interface will come in which it will
show the name of your bike zone, it will show the third
day plan and the third party
validity will be shown to you, from when till when it is
valid, like you can see in this that it
is connected from July till 2030 and
you will have to pay Rs. 1408 here, if
you click on the i button here then
you will see that this basic third
party liability premium is Rs. 1193
and first demand and friends, you
should know this, then you can see this,
after that you click here
friends, you can use it or you
will cut it, so here we have to click
that personality insurance purchase for Rs.
1408 is very successful, our policy is
insurance, it is infallible and very soon
this policy certificate will be sent to your
email  If you get it, then you have to click on
Done here and then you have to come from the cow or buffalo's stomach,
friends, after that
you can see in our policy status
that you will see Active, you have to
click on this icon here,
after clicking you will
see Active from here and then if you want to
see the policy certificate, then this
policy certificate number can also be seen from here
and when you click on the policy document,
you will see this here
and here you will be asked
whether your policy should be
sent on sending an email, then you have to click on the button from here
and the policy status, this
policy world, the policy paper will have been
sent to your email, then you
can check it by going here, friends, after that
if you want to keep the paper of whatever you have done on your phone
with your vehicle, then you have to open your email,
after opening it you will get a
download option of the
policy here and take the tiffin top,
when now you will see the
paper of your policy, you can see it
here  You can check it from here and download it
and keep it with the vehicle, so
it is completely valid, there is no
legal problem with it,
you can use it in this way, so
friends, this was today's video in which you
saw how we
can search for the solution of any work in a very short time
and save our precious time and money,
thank you very much for watching the video.